hey guys and welcome back to the channel
today i am doing a little unboxing of
this vacuum i ordered this is the heart
pro bagless upright vacuum cleaner
and i ordered this off the walmart
website and it runs about 89
on there right now they're still having
a so i actually got this on their uh
that black friday sale but the sale is
still on and it normally runs about 150
but right now you can get it for 89
bucks so yeah y'all i'm gonna go get my
knife and open this up
gotta put a little elbow grease into it
y'all
oh okay
[Applause]
[Music]
look at this
okay
this is cool
got some weight it's got some weight to
it y'all
so this looks pretty easy to assemble
it's only a couple little extra pieces
on there
but i'm gonna look at the little book
just to make sure that i'm doing it
right
all right guys so this is what it looks
like just out the box
so i'm gonna have to put these few
pieces together
i'm gonna look at the manual real quick
and
see what i need to do but it looks
pretty simple
hey guys so i was looking over the
manual and this is the extension wand
now this can be used a couple different
ways and let me tell you guys this
everything really is already together
you just this is like the missing piece
to everything okay so the first way you
can use this extension wand is you can
just go ahead and put it
in the back
all right just put it in the back of the
vacuum and just stick it down in there
okay
and then take your top this piece right
here
and stick it on top
and there it's just what i said in
extension one it extends the little um
vacuum it just extends it up for you
okay and the second way
that you can use it
is you just pull it out thing in the
back that says wand you just want to
pull down here let me take my camera let
me show you guys so in the back there's
a little button that says one you just
want to pull that back and then pull the
one up out of there okay just pull up on
the one it'll come right on out
like that like so
but i can only have two hands but yeah
you just pull this button and the one
will come right on out
here's your power button right here and
here's your dirt cut release button
and you just would push this
and it'll go ahead and release
and then all you have to do
is there's a little button where's the
button okay here it is the buttons in
the back you just press the button
and sorry guys this i only have two
hands but you just press the button
and then over make sure you're over a
trash bin and just dump everything out
so this is pretty easy let me finish
telling you guys what the extension one
what else the extension one can do
all right guys so i have took my
extension one out
and it's still connected to the handle
the little handle in the uh vacuum tube
so what we can do
with the um
with the extension one
you can put your crevice tool
on top to get into those little
corners and little crevices
that just goes
i just just push that down on there
and so
you can get into your little crevices
with that
right
and then the other thing you can do
this on there good
you can put your pet brush on there
right i don't have a pet but i like
getting these pet vacuums because they
get up hair really really good
and you can put this on there
and yeah and just get to going and they
say that this actually stretches up 14
feet
so yeah yeah i'm gonna try it out and
i'm not gonna try i'm not gonna turn it
on on camera because i feel like the
sound would be too loud and yeah i
really don't know how to edit so i don't
know how i wouldn't know how to like
mess with the volumes and all that and i
don't want you guys to ears like if
you're listening with headphones i don't
want that shock value going through your
ears so yeah i'm gonna test this out off
camera and then i will come back and i
will let you know my thoughts on it but
so far
i really like it like it was so simple
to put together this was really the only
piece that you had to put in there and
everything else it's basically already
built it's very easy there's no bag for
clean up
so
yeah so far i'm liking it all i got to
do is take it for a test run and i will
be right back after i do that okay guys
all right
okay guys so i am back with my final
thoughts on this product and y'all i
really like it now let me tell y'all
first things first when i started vacuum
vacuuming the front of it
started lighting up this has little
light so
if you're light if you're vacuuming at
night you don't have to turn on lights
because guess what your vacuum has
lights on the front okay i've never had
a vacuum with lights on it so i'm a
little geeked up right now all right
next thing um
something that is fine but threw me off
a little bit is the power button is up
here i'm used to the power button being
down here me just stepping on it and
vacuum so i got to get used to that
because when i went to go vacuum i put
my foot right here and there was no like
turn on button it's right there and when
you put it up when you press the power
button like actually press it down good
and then it'll come on the other thing
also i'm used to a little button like a
little click button being either on this
side on this side to navigate um
to lean it back to lean the vacuum back
but right here is where you put your
foot
and then just press down
and then pull
pull back
and then it kind of will go
any way you want it to go
so yeah i thought that was pretty cool
let's get that back
there we go
yeah so all in all
i really like this it got up it cleaned
good there's a little dust ball in there
oh my god ew
but yeah y'all this thing is the truth
and only 89
and yeah this is not a sponsor video
this is me giving y'all my honest
opinion i would fully recommend this
this vacuum this is like one of the best
vacuums that i've had and it's one of
the cheaper vacuums that i've ever
bought
so yeah y'all i'm very happy with my
purchase thank you heart this is a
really good product um yeah guys and
that's going to be the end of the video
if you could if you feel it on your
heart please like comment and subscribe
and let me know if you have heart
products or if you have this vacuum like
y'all i'm really feeling this vacuum
anyway guys i hope that you guys are
doing well and being blessed and as
always i will see you guys in my next
video alright y'all bye